gandi.net 2017-06-30

# 

                                                              Gandi Privacy Policy
Last updated August 1, 2014 – Version 1.0
Thank you for visiting our Privacy Policy. This policy applies to information collected on gandi.net and all affiliated websites that link to
this Policy (collectively referred to herein as the "Sites", “Gandi”, "we" or "us").
Gandi is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of those who entrust us with their personal information. Visitors to our Sites, our
customers and all those who do business with us trust and expect that we will protect their personal information. We want you to know
that we take the privacy, security and confidentiality of your information, including any personally identifiable information ("Personal
Data" or "PII") extremely seriously. Accordingly, we take all commercially practicable and available precautions to ensure the security
and confidentiality of Personal Data.
We also want you to know what information we collect, why and how we will treat it once collected. Finally, we want you to be able to
have control over your Personal Data so that if you need to update or to correct your information or want to opt-out of receiving certain
communications, you can do that easily. In short, this Privacy Policy is for you. Please read it carefully.
CONSENT:
BY ACCESSING THE SITES AND/OR CREATING A GANDI ACCOUNT OR ALLOWING SOMEONE TO USE THE SITES ON YOUR
BEHALF, YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE COLLECTION, USE, DISCLOSURE, TRANSFER AND STORAGE OF PERSONAL
AND NON-PERSONAL DATA OR OTHER INFORMATION RECEIVED BY US AS A RESULT OF SUCH USE IN ACCORDANCE
WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY.
Your California Privacy Rights, Our Contact Info & Requests                 you own or have owned. This information is used to provide the
for Information                                                             services that you have requested and to suggest additional
                                                                            services that we believe you may be interested in.
It is vitally important for you to keep your Personal Data accurate,       We may collect your name, email address, mailing address, zip
current and complete at all times, as well as for you to be able to         code, and date of birth if you create an account with us. This
reach us should you have any questions or concerns regarding                information will be used to help you keep track of your orders, to
this privacy policy. If we are unable to address your issue
                                                                            keep you updated about special offers, updates related to the
immediately, we will respond as soon as possible.
                                                                            Sites and any of the Gandi Contracts or other agreements which
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents         are applicable to the products or services you have purchased
of California can obtain certain information about the types of PII         or to which you have subscribed, and to facilitate checkout
that companies with whom they have an established business                  during purchases.
relationship have shared with third parties for direct marketing           We may collect your email address if you sign up to receive
purposes during the preceding calendar year. In particular, that            promotional emails from us. This information may be used to
law provides that consumers may request a copy of the PII that we
                                                                            contact you about sales, special offers and new features
hold about you. Consumers may also request information
                                                                            available through the Sites.
regarding the categories of PII that have been shared with third
parties, the names and addresses of those third parties and                We may collect your name, telephone number, mailing address,
examples of the types of services or products marketed by those             zip code, and email address if you contact us with a question or
third parties. To request either a copy of the PII maintained by us         request customer support from us. This information may be
about you or to request a copy of the information disclosure                used so that we can respond to your question or contact you
provided by us during the preceding calendar year pursuant to               regarding your request.
Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us via        We may collect your name, email address, and other contact
emailt at: us-privacy@gandi.net, or by writing us at the below              information if you participate in a promotion (e.g., contest,
address. Please allow 30 days for a response.                               sweepstakes) that we sponsor. This information will be used to
                             Gandi US, Inc.                                 fulfill the terms of the promotion and to contact you regarding
                            Attention: Privacy                              promotional and special offers, sales, and new features
                           121 2nd St. Ste 500                              available through the Sites. It will also be subject to the terms
                       San Francisco, CA 94105                              accompanying such promotion.
                         Phone: (410) 429-7400                             We may collect your name, age, zip code, purchasing habits,
                          Fax: (410) 429-7400                               email address and/or mailing address if you choose to
                                                                            participate in one of our on-line surveys. This information will be
What Information Is Collected?                                              used to help provide us with relevant information about our
1. Personal Data                                                            customers.
                                                                           We may collect and maintain more extensive PII (including
We may collect Personal Data from users of the Sites in several
                                                                            driver’s license numbers, passport numbers, social security
instances. Some examples are as follows:
                                                                            numbers, etc.) if you are purchasing a Gandi SSL Certificate, as
 We may collect your name, billing address, shipping address,              we are required to review proof of identification and related
   email address, telephone number. This information is used to             documentation to verify your identity in order to issue you the
   provide the products and services that you have ordered or               Gandi SSL Certificate for which you are applying.
   requested and order confirmations (or other transactional               We may collect and maintain more extensive PII (including
   information) and/or to provide customer service.                         driver’s license numbers, passport numbers, social security
 We may collect information regarding the domain names that                numbers, etc.) if you are purchasing some extensions (domain
                                                                                                                                             1/5

   names) which require supporting documentation.                    to store your account information as this information is stored
                                                                     securely on a server. When you log in at the Sites with your
Of course, you can update your information or change your            username and password, we will assign you a secure session id.
preferences regarding receiving announcements and other              The server then passes your information to you through this
information from us at any time by accessing your account via the    secure session id. Cookies may be session cookies (i.e., last only
Sites. (For more information, see below section entitled How Can I   for one browser session) or persistent cookies (i.e., continue in
Access, Correct and Update My Personal Information?)                 your browser until they are deleted or expire). Some of the cookies
                                                                     we use may be flash cookies or Adobe cookies. While they are
The above section provides examples of the Personal Data that        harmless, they may contain demographic information and
we may collect through the Sites and the manners in which we         depending on your browser these cookies may not normally be
may use such Personal Data. If you do not want us to collect your    deleted when your cookies are deleted. Please check your
Personal Data, please do not provide it to us.                       browser to determine where these types of cookies are stored and
2. Non-Personal Data                                                 how they may be deleted.
You do not need to create an account with us to use the Sites.       While we recommend that you leave cookies turned on as they
When you use the Sites, including by browsing our merchandise        allow you to take advantage of some of the features of the Sites,
and/or contacting us with inquiries, we collect certain non-         you have the ability to control the use and moderation of our
identifiable information ("Non-Personal Data"). The Non-Personal     cookies. However, if you elect not to allow cookies to be placed as
Data we collect includes, without limitation, Internet Protocol (IP) provided herein, you may not be able to use or to enjoy all of the
addresses, Internet browser information, other characteristics of    services and features of the Sites. Specifically, you can configure
your device and software, domain names of your Internet Service      the settings (i) to receive notifications when you are receiving new
Provider (ISP), your approximate geographic location, a record of    cookies, (ii) to disable cookies or (iii) to delete cookies. Please
your usage of our Sites, the time of your usage and aggregated       refer to your Web browser's help section for information on how to
Personal Data that cannot be used to specifically identify you.      do this.
Such information, which is collected passively using various          Other Websites, Including Mobile Applications and Social Media
technologies, cannot, in and of itself, be used to specifically
                                                                        Platforms:
identify you. This information is used to analyze and to improve
the Sites (including to help diagnose and prevent problems with
                                                                     If you use a social media platform or your mobile device (or other
our servers or our products or services), to administer our Site and
                                                                     method of communication) to interact with the Sites, that platform
to provide our customers with the best experience using our Site.
                                                                     or application may have a specific privacy statement that governs
We also may receive certain Non-Personal Data (including,
                                                                     the use of Personal Data related to it. If you have questions about
without limitation, of the types set forth above) from various third
                                                                     the security and privacy settings of your mobile device, please
parties. The Non-Personal Data we receive from third parties may
                                                                     refer to instructions from your mobile service provider or the
be combined with the information we collect as specified herein,
                                                                     manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.
including Personal Data. If Non-Personal Data is combined with
                                                                     We do not control the data collection or privacy practices of any
Personal Data, it may be viewed as Personal Data. However,
                                                                     third-party platform through which you access the Sites or contact
where the data remains non-personally identifiable, it will still be
                                                                     us. You should review the privacy policy and terms of use of any
viewed as Non-Personal Data. We provide additional information
                                                                     third-party site before using it and review and use available
on our Non-Personal Data collection below:
                                                                     controls and settings on your device to reflect your preferences.
 Cookies and Other Session Identifiers:                             How Can I Access, Correct and Update My Personal
                                                                     Information?
Like many sites, we utilize a technology called "cookies". A cookie
is a piece of information that is placed on your browser when you    You can access, correct and/or update certain personal
access the Sites. In many cases, the information collected using     information that you have provided by logging into your Gandi
cookies (and related technologies) are used in non-identifiable      Account with your Access Codes.
ways, without any reference to Personal Data. For example, we        How Do We Use the Information Collected?
use information we collect about users of the Sites to optimize our
Sites and to understand traffic and usage patterns. In other cases,  1. Personal Data
we associate the information we collect using cookies and related
                                                                     We may use Personal Data as necessary and to fulfill your
technologies with Personal Data. In that case, this Privacy Policy
                                                                     requests, including in the following ways:
governs how we use that information. Additionally, if the settings
on your location-aware device allow us to receive geo-location       Access and Use: If you provide Personal Data in order to obtain
data or information, we may collect that information automatically.  access to or use of the Sites or any functionality thereof, we will
We also use tracking information to determine which areas our        use your Personal Data to provide you with access to or use of the
site users visit based on traffic to those areas. Gandi does not     Sites or functionality and to monitor your use of the Sites or
track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is  specific functionalities.
visited.
                                                                     Internal Business Purposes: We may use your Personal Data for
Cookies help provide additional functionality to the Sites and help  internal business purposes including, without limitation, to help us
us to more accurately analyze usage of the Sites. For instance,      improve the content and functionality of the Sites, to better
the Sites may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to        understand our users, to improve the Sites, to protect against,
access the Sites during future visits. We use cookies to monitor     identify or address fraudulent activities, to manage your account
and to maintain information about your use of the Sites. Cookies     and to provide you with customer service and to generally manage
are also used to track the identity of the website you visited       the Sites and our business.
immediately prior to visiting the Sites; other than that, we do not
                                                                     Marketing: We may use your Personal Data to contact you for
track information about your use of other websites. Cookies also
                                                                     certain marketing and advertising purposes, including, without
allow us to hold selections in a shopping cart when a user leaves
                                                                     limitation, to inform you about offers, contests or surveys which
the Sites without checking out. Cookies are not used on the Sites
                                                                     may be of interest to you and to display content and advertising on
                                                                                                                                       2/5

or off the Sites which may be of relevance to you. If you wish to with the services they are retained to perform. We employ a
change or update your Personal Data or to change your vetting process to ensure that our partners adhere to exacting
subscription preferences, you may do so as provided herein.           data security and privacy standards.
Specific Reason: If you provide Personal Data for a certain           Legal Requirements: We may disclose your Personal Data if
reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the           required to do so by law (including, without limitation responding to
reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by  a subpoena or request from law enforcement, court or government
email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your       agency) or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary (i)
question or to attempt to resolve your issue and will respond to the  to comply with a legal obligation, (ii) to protect or defend our rights,
email address from which the contact came.                            interests or property or that of other customers or users, (iii) to act
                                                                      in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of
Aggregated Personal Data: In an ongoing effort to better
                                                                      the Sites or the public, or (iv) to protect against legal liability or
understand and to serve the users of the Sites, we (either directly
                                                                      potential fraud, as determined in our sole discretion.
or working in concert with our marketing services providers) may
conduct research on our customer demographics, interests and Other uses: If we intend to use any Personal Data in any manner
behavior based on Personal Data and other information that has that is not specified herein, we will inform you of such anticipated
been provided or received by us. For example, we may combine use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected
information about visitors to the Sites to determine how best to or we will obtain your consent subsequent to such collection but
target our marketing and the products and services that we offer in prior to such use. In short, we will honor the choices you make
certain areas of the country. This research may be compiled and regarding your Personal Data and will inform you about any other
analyzed on an aggregate basis and this aggregate information intended uses of such information.
does not identify you personally and is classified and treated as
                                                                      2. Non-Personal Data
Non-Personal Data under this Privacy Policy.
                                                                      As noted above, Non-Personal Data does not and cannot be used
Do We Share Your Information?
                                                                      to personally identify you. We may use such information for any
We are not in the business of selling Personal Data. We consider lawful purpose, including sharing Non-Personal Data with our
this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. We marketing partners, advertisers and others from time to time.
do not share with others, or sell or rent to others, any Personal Examples of such Non-Personal Data include the number of users
Data provided to us through the Sites or through our Customer who visited the Sites during a specific time period or purchased a
Service Department, except with your consent or as described in specific product or service through the Sites. This information
this Privacy Policy. Additionally, we seek to receive your consent generally is shared in an aggregated form.
before sharing your information. However, in some cases, your
                                                                      What Steps Are Taken To Keep My Information Secure?
permission will be implied from the nature of the service requested
or transaction undertaken. Examples of instances in which we We have implemented information security measures that contain
share your Personal Data are provided below:                          administrative, technical and physical controls that are designed to
                                                                      reasonably safeguard Personal and Non-Personal Data. Even
Order Fulfillment: If you choose to make a purchase on the Sites,
                                                                      though we have taken and will continue to take significant steps to
we may collect from you billing address and other information
                                                                      protect this information, no company, including us, can fully
related to such purchase, and we may use such collected
                                                                      eliminate all security risks associated with Personal Data.
information in order to fulfill your purchase. We may also provide
such information, or other Personal Data provided by you, to We use various security measures, including Secure Socket Layer
unaffiliated third parties as necessary to complete your purchase.    (SSL) encryption technology, to protect information collected,
                                                                      transferred and retained. If you elect to set up an account on the
Business Transfers: As with any business, it is possible that as our
                                                                      Sites, you will be asked to provide an email address and
business develops, we might sell, assign, buy, transfer or
                                                                      password. You must provide a valid email address and password
otherwise acquire or dispose of certain businesses or corporate
                                                                      in order to create and maintain an account, as well as to access
assets. In the event of such or similar event, Personal Data may
                                                                      account information. We recommend you select a password with
be part of the transferred assets. You acknowledge and agree that
                                                                      at least 8 characters and consider adding numbers or special
any successor to or acquirer of us will continue to have the right to
                                                                      characters to further strengthen your password. In order to help
use your Personal Data and other information in accordance with
                                                                      protect your personal information, you should be careful about
the terms of this Privacy Policy.
                                                                      providing your password to others and change it periodically. If
Parent, Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We may also share your you wish to update a password, or if you become aware of any
Personal Data with our parent company, subsidiaries and/or loss, theft or unauthorized use of a password, please contact us at
affiliates consistent with this Privacy Policy. Our subsidiaries and us-privacy@gandi.net.
affiliates will be bound to treat and to maintain any Personal Data
                                                                      Please be aware that we may store Personal Data or such
in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
                                                                      information may be included in databases owned and maintained
Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: As noted above, by our affiliates, agents or third party service providers. We take
we, like many businesses, sometimes engage other companies to all commercially reasonable steps to protect the security and
perform certain business-related functions on our behalf so that confidentiality of all Personal Data provided via the Sites from
we can focus on our core business. Examples of these services loss, misuse, unauthorized access, inadvertent disclosure,
include, but are not limited to, payment processing and alteration and/or destruction.
authorization, fraud protection and credit risk reduction, product
                                                                      However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or
customization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing and
                                                                      error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Sites may not
promotional material distribution, website evaluation, data analysis
                                                                      always be secure. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any
and, where applicable, data cleansing.
                                                                      Personal Data via the Internet or by email.
In connection with services those partners provide for us, we may
                                                                      We do not and will not, at any time, ask you to provide your
provide or otherwise give them access to certain Personal Data,
                                                                      Personal Data or other personal information in a non-secure or
but we authorize them to use this information only in connection
                                                                      unsolicited email or telephone communication. Identity theft and
                                                                                                                                           3/5

the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to    POLICY DOES NOT COVER THE COLLECTION AND USE OF
us. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft  INFORMATION BY SUCH ADVERTISING COMPANIES.
is one of our priorities. If you receive such an email, please
                                                                      What Happens When I Link To or From Another Website?
contact us to bring it to our attention. For more information about
phishin g, v isit the F edera l Tra de C ommissio n at                The Sites may contain links to other websites not operated or
http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0003-phishing.                   controlled by us (the "Third Party Sites"). The policies and
                                                                      procedures set forth herein do not apply to any Third Party Sites.
What Choices Do I Have Regarding my Personal Data?
                                                                      The owners and operators of all Third Party Sites are responsible
You have several choices available when it comes to your              for all Personal Data and Non-Personal Data provided, collected,
Personal Data. We will honor the choices you make regarding           maintained, stored or otherwise disclosed on those sites, if any.
your Personal Data. If you have created and maintained a Gandi        The links on the Sites do not imply that we endorse or have
Account on the Sites, you will be able to sign in and update your     reviewed the Third Party Sites, including their privacy policies, if
account (including contact) information. You may also write to us     any. We strongly encourage contacting those sites directly for
at the address provided herein and update your contact                information on their privacy policies.
information or to change your subscription preferences. In
                                                                      If you have accessed the Sites through a link from certain of our
addition, you may:
                                                                      advertising or marketing partners, the Sites may include a frame of
Limit the Personal Data You Provide: You can use the Sites and the applicable advertising or marketing partner. Nevertheless, the
limit the Personal Data you provide either by disabling cookies or information you provide to us through these framed Web pages is
by not registering an account with us. If you choose to limit the collected by us, and our use of such information is governed by
Personal Data you provide and/or to disable cookies, you may not this Privacy Policy.
be able to use certain functionalities of the Sites. For instance, in
                                                                      How Do We Respond to Do Not Track Signals?
order to purchase goods and services on the Sites, payment and
shipping information must necessarily be provided.                    Please note that our Sites do not support “Do Not Track” browser
                                                                      settings and do not currently participate in any “Do Not Track”
Manage your Subscription Preferences: We may send you
                                                                      frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other
information by email if you subscribe via your Gandi Account. You
                                                                      mechanisms from you regarding the collection of your personal or
further understand that consent is not a condition of purchase and
                                                                      non-personally identifiable information.
that message and data rates may apply. Additional terms and
conditions.                                                           Is Information Collected From Children?
Please be aware that even if you opt-out of receiving future          Protecting the privacy of children is extremely important to us. The
promotional communications, you may, if you utilize the               Sites are directed toward a general audience and are not directed
eCommerce features of the Sites, be sent certain transactional        at nor intended for use by children. We do not knowingly collect or
communications related to the purchase or shipment of items           intend to collect Personal Data from anyone who is under the age
purchased. Thus, if you order online, we will send you an email       of 13. If you are under the age of 13, you should not provide any
confirming your order and may need to contact you by phone,           Personal Data to us and you should use the Sites only with the
email or regular mail if we have questions about your order.          knowledge, permission and involvement of a parent or guardian.
Additionally, an opt-out will not remove you from messages that       We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their
we are required to send under relevant laws or regulations.           children's Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by
                                                                      instructing their children never to provide Personal Data through
Social Media & Other Public Platforms: You may also manage the
                                                                      the Sites. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age
sharing of certain Personal Data with us when you connect with us
                                                                      of 13 has provided Personal Data to us, please contact us and we
through a social media platform or application, such as through
                                                                      will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.
Facebook Connect. Please refer to the privacy settings of the
social media website or application to determine how you may What if I Access the Sites from Outside of the United States?
adjust your permissions and manage the interactivity between us
and your social media platform(s) or application(s). When you post If you are visiting our Sites from outside the United States, please
information to public forums, including publicly viewable social be aware that you are sending information (including Personal
media platforms, that information will become available to all who Data) to the United States where some of our servers are located.
access such platform pages. PLEASE BE EXTREMELY We have agreed to abide by the Safe Harbor Agreement between
CAREFUL WHEN DISCLOSING ANY INFORMATION IN CHAT the United States and the European Union, with respect to
ROOMS, FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS. WE personal data processed by United States companies as part of its
ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE BY OTHERS OF THE regular business activities. This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy sets
INFORMATION THAT YOU DISCLOSE IN CHAT ROOMS, forth how Gandi US, Inc. handles personal data transferred from
FORUMS AND OTHER PUBLIC POSTING AREAS.                                countries in the European Economic Area (EEA) to the United
                                                                      States that are collected or received in connection with of our
Third Party Advertisers: We may use advertisers, third party ad business.
networks, and other advertising companies, to serve
advertisements on our Sites and on third-party websites. Please Otherwise, we will hold and process your Personal Data and Non-
be advised that such advertising companies may gather Personal Data in accordance with privacy laws in the United
information about your visit to our Sites (such as through cookies, States and this Privacy Policy. Please note that privacy laws in the
web beacons and other technologies) to enable such advertising United States may not be the same as, and in some cases may be
companies to market products or services to you, to monitor which considered less protective than, privacy laws in other countries.
ads have been served to your browser and which web pages you Therefore, by providing your Personal Data, you consent to the
were viewing when such ads were delivered. If you would like use of your Personal Data for the uses identified in this Privacy
more information about this practice and to know your choices         Policy and to the transfer of your Personal Data to the United
                                                                      States as indicated above.
please                                                       visit:
http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp             or How Will I Be Informed About Changes Regarding This
http://preferences.truste.com/truste/. PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS Privacy Policy?
                                                                                                                                        4/5

The Sites and our business may change from time to time. As a           be available in court. A single neutral arbitrator shall be selected in
result (and for other business and/or technological reasons), it        accordance with the JAMS Streamlined Arbitration Rules, which
may be necessary for us to make changes to this Privacy Policy.         shall provide you a reasonable opportunity to participate in the
We reserve the right to update, change, amend or modify this            arbitrator selection. The parties to arbitration will have full right to
Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior          use legal counsel at their own expense. All costs of arbitration
notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before   (including arbitrator fees) shall be paid by Gandi, except only that
you provide any Personal Data.                                          if you bring the arbitration, you may be charged an initial filing fee
                                                                        that shall not exceed the filing fees that you would incur for
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy (as
                                                                        bringing an action in court. You will not be required to pay fees and
determined by us), we will post a notice on the Sites notifying
                                                                        costs incurred by the opposing parties if you do not prevail in
users of the changes and providing an opportunity for you to take
                                                                        arbitration. In arbitration, the parties may conduct reasonable
action relative to those changes prior to their implementation. In
                                                                        discovery and shall reasonably exchange non-privileged
some cases, we also may send a notice via the Gandi Account or
                                                                        information relevant to the dispute. The arbitrator’s award shall be
by email notifying registered users of upcoming changes.
                                                                        in writing and provide a written statement of the essential findings
This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above.       and conclusions. The arbitrator will not have the power to commit
Your continued use of the Sites after any changes or revisions to       any error of law or legal reasoning, and the award may be vacated
this Privacy Policy become effective shall indicate your agreement      or corrected on appeal to a court of competent jurisdiction for any
with the terms of such revised and then-current Privacy Policy.         such error. As an exception to this arbitration provision, no one
                                                                        subject to the provision will be precluded from seeking remedies in
                                                                        small claims court for disputes or claims within the scope of its
Arbitration; Claims Must be Brought on an Individual Basis              jurisdiction. Claims brought on behalf of or allegedly representing
                                                                        or including other persons or entities, including but not limited to
By using this Sites, you agree that any dispute in any manner           any class, consolidated, representative, collective, or private
arising out of or relating in any way to this Privacy Policy, its       attorney general action, shall be a “Class Action.” Notwithstanding
enforcement or interpretation, or because of an alleged breach,         anything else in this Privacy Policy or the JAMS rules, any parties
default, or misrepresentation in connection with any of its             subject to this arbitration provision shall be barred from bringing or
provisions, shall be submitted to binding arbitration with Judicial     participating in any Class Action for a dispute covered by this
Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc. (“JAMS”) in the San            arbitration provision. However, if these Class Actions restrictions
Francisco Bay/San Jose, California area. This arbitration provision     are ever deemed illegal, they shall be severed from this arbitration
is equally binding on claims brought by Gandi as on claims              provision. In that event, any Class Action shall be exempted from
brought by you or others. Arbitrations will be conducted under the      this arbitration provision and brought in court. This arbitration
applicable JAMS rules. The parties to arbitration will have all the     provision is subject to the Federal Arbitration Act, and may be
same claims, legal rights, and remedies in arbitration that would       enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction.
                                                       -- end of the Privacy Policy --
                                                 © 2014 Gandi US, Inc. All rights reserved.
                                                                                                                                              5/5
